大家好，我们开始吧
alright hello everyone let's get started
今天的话题是因果一致性，然后使用警察制度
today the topic is causal consistency
and then use the cop system the cop's
我们每天的论文都是因果一致性的案例研究，因此
paper that we're every day is a case
study for causal consistency so the
设置实际上很熟悉，我们再次谈论大型网站
setting is actually familiar we're
talking again about big websites that
在多个数据中心中有数据，他们想在每个数据中心中复制数据
have data in multiple data centers and
they want to replicate the data in each
每个数据中心的所有数据都必须保存副本
of their all their data in each their
data centers have to keep a copy close
给用户，也许是为了容错，所以像往常一样，我们可能会
to users and for perhaps for fault
tolerance so as usual we have maybe I'll
有三个数据中心
have three data centers
而且您知道，因为我们正在构建大型系统，所以我们将分片数据
and you know because we're building big
systems we're going to shard the data
每个数据中心都将有多台服务器，您可能都知道
and every data center is going to have
multiple servers with you know maybe all
以Z a开头的所有托管人对应分片的密钥
the keys that start with Z a through all
the custodian corresponding shards of
我们已经看到过的URL，您知道人们知道的通常目标
URLs we've seen this for and you know
the usual goals people have you know
如何进行这项工作有很多不同的设计，但您知道吗
there's many different designs for how
to make this work but you know you
真的很喜欢阅读，当然也很喜欢阅读，因为这些网站
really like reads to be certainly like
reads to be fast because these web
工作负载往往以阅读为主，并且您知道自己想要工作和
workloads tend to be read dominated and
you know you'd like rights to work and
您想让我们尽可能地保持一致
you'd like to have us as much
consistency as you can so the fast
原因很有趣，因为客户端通常是Web浏览器，因此
reasons are interesting because the
clients are typically web browsers so
网络将有一组网络浏览器，所有这些浏览器都将客户端称为
and there's web going to be some set of
web browsers which all call clients the
客户端存储系统，但它们实际上是与用户
clients the storage system but they're
really web browsers talking to a user's
浏览器，所以典型的安排是这些发生在本地的原因
browser some so the typical arrangement
is that the reason these happen locally
权利可能会稍微复杂一点，因此适合这种情况的系统
and rights might be little more
complicated so one system that fits this
模式是扳手，您还记得涉及的扳手和扳手权利
pattern is spanner you remember that a
spanner and spanner rights involved
运行在所有数据中心的Paxos，因此如果您在paxos中进行写操作
Paxos that runs across all the data
centers so if you do a write in paxos
也许数据中心的客户需要写一份涉及通信的文件
maybe a client in a data center needs to
do a write the communication involve
实际需要税收可能在这些服务器之一上运行以进行通话
actually need requires taxes maybe
running on one of these servers to talk
至少要复制到其他大多数数据中心，因此权利
to at least a majority of the other data
centers that are replicas so the rights
往往会有点慢，但除此之外，萨凡纳（Savannah）支持
tend to be a little bit slow but there
consistent in addition Savannah supports
两阶段提交，因此我们有事务，读取速度更快，因为
two-phase commit so we had transactions
and the reads are much faster because
微风使用了真正的时间计划，论文的跨度描述了
the breeze used a true time scheme that
the span of paper described and really
只咨询了当地人，我们还阅读了Facebook内存缓存的新论文，该论文是
only consulted local we also read the
Facebook memcache new paper which is
在此演示模式中的另一种设计Facebook memcache关键文件中有一个
another design in this demo pattern the
Facebook memcache key paper there's a
具有我的续集数据库的主要集合的主站点，因此如果客户想要
primary site that has the primary set of
my sequel databases so if a client wants
做正确的事，我想这个数据中心3的主要方面是发送所有
to do a right I suppose the primary side
this data center 3 does to send all
数据中心3的权限，然后数据中心3发送新信息或
rights to data center 3 and then data
center 3 sends out new information or in
对其他数据中心的验证正确，因此实际上有点贵
validations to the other data centers
right so actually a little bit expensive
与另一方面的扳手不同，当客户端时所有读取都是本地的
and not unlike spanner on the other hand
all the reads are local when a client
需要做一个珠子，它可以查询本地数据中的内存缓存密钥服务器
needs to do a bead it could consult a
memcache key server in the local data
中心，还有memcachedb先生，这让人眼花fast乱
center and there's memcachedb sir just
blindingly fast this the people
向他们报告单个内存缓存，服务器每次保存一百万次读取
reporting them a single memcache the
server conserve a million reads per
第二个非常快，因此Facebook memcache D方案也需要
second which is very fast so again the
Facebook memcache D scheme needs to
涉及跨数据通信中心的权利，但阅读
involve cross data center of
communication for rights but the reads
是本地的，所以今天的问题和警察文件的问题
are local so the question for today and
the question of the cops papers
答案是我们是否可以拥有允许权利追究的制度
answering is whether we can have a
system that allows rights to pursue
纯粹在本地，从客户的角度来看，客户可以交谈
purely locally and this from the clients
point of views that the client can talk
从正确到正确，他们可以自己发送正确的本地副本
to the from once it were right they can
send the right local replica in its own
数据中心以及某些读取仅本地副本，而永远不会
data center as well as some reads to
just the local replicas and never have
等待其他数据中心无需与其他数据中心对话
to wait for other data centers never
have to talk to other data centers or
等待其他数据中心行使权利，所以我们真正想要的是一个
wait for other data centers to do rights
so what we really want is a system that
可以具有本地读取和本地权限
can have local reads and local rights
那是大目标这是大目标实际上是一个绩效目标
that's the big that's the big goal
really a performance goal this would
当然可以帮助提高性能，因为与以前的扳手和Facebook论文不同
help for performance of course cuz now
unlike spanner and Facebook paper we had
从客户的角度来看，纯粹的本地权利要快得多
a purely local rights be much faster
from the clients point of view um it
如果可以在本地完成权限，则还可能有助于提高容错能力
might also help with fault tolerance
robustness if rights can be done locally
那么我们不必担心其他数据中心是否正常运行或
then we don't have to worry about
whether other data centers are up or
是否可以快速与他们交谈，因为客户不需要等待
whether we can talk to them quickly
because the clients don't need to wait
为他们服务，所以我们将要寻找具有这种水平的系统
for them so we're gonna be looking for
systems that have this this level of
性能，最后我们将让您知道的一致性模型
performance and in the end we're gonna
let the consistency model you know cuz
如果您只行使权利，我们将担心一致性
we're going to be worried about
consistency if you only do the rights
首先到本地副本，您知道其他数据中心副本的情况
initially to the local replicas you know
what about other data centers replicas
数据，所以我们一定会担心一致性
data so we'll certainly be worried about
consistency
但是至少本次演讲的态度是我们要让
but the attitude for this lecture at
least is that we're gonna let the
一旦我们弄清楚，一致性跟踪就会跟踪您知道的性能
consistency trail along behind the
performance you know once we figure out
如何获得良好的表现，然后就会弄清楚如何定义
how to get good performance will well
then sort of figure out how to define
在考虑是否足够好方面保持一致性，这就是整体
consistency in think about whether it's
good enough okay so that's the overall
我实际上会谈论两种稻草人设计的策略，但是
strategy I'm gonna actually talk about
two strawman designs to sort of okay but
在我们实际谈论警察如何工作之前的途中，设计不是很好
not great designs on the way to before
we actually talk about how cops works so
首先，我想谈一个遵循该本地评级的最简单的设计
first i want to talk about a simplest
design that follows this local rating
我能想到的策略我将这个稻草人称为1
strategy that I can think of I'll call
this straw man 1 so in straw and one
我们将拥有三个数据中心
we're going to have three data centers
并假设每种数据以两种方式绘制图表，因此他
and let's just assume that the data is
charted two ways in each of them so he's
也许是ATM机和大使馆的钥匙在每个
from maybe ATM and keys from embassy
shard it the same way in each of the
数据中心和客户端将在本地读取，如果客户端写入
data centers and the clients will read
locally and if a client writes so
假设客户需要编写以M开头的密钥，客户将
supposing a client needs to write it key
that starts with M the clients gonna
将密钥M的写入发送到具有以下内容的本地分片服务器的分片服务器
send a write of key M to the shard
server the local shard server that has
它负责以分片服务器返回回复的M开始
its responsible he's starting with M
that shard server would return reply to
客户立即说哦，是的，我是对的，但除此之外
the client immediately saying oh yes I
did you're right but in addition each
服务器将维护已发送的未决权利队列
server will maintain a queue of
outstanding rights that have been sent
它最近得到了需要发送到其他数据中心的客户，并且它
to it recently got clients that it needs
to send to other data centers and it
会将这些权利在后台异步流式传输到相应的权限
will stream these rights asynchronously
in the background to the corresponding
其他数据中心中的服务器，因此在向客户应用我们的分片之后
servers in the other data center so
after applying to the client our shard
此处的服务器将向其他每个数据发送客户端权限的副本
server here will send a copy of the
clients right to each of the other data
设置，您知道这些权利会通过网络传播，也许他们需要
setups and you know those rights go
through the network maybe they take a
很长一段时间，他们最终将到达目标数据集
long time eventually they're gonna
arrive at the target data set the other
数据中心以及这些分片服务器中的每一个都将对该服务器应用权限
data centers and each of those shard
servers will then apply the right to its
本地数据表，因此这是一种具有非常好的性能的设计
local table of data so this is a design
that has very good performance right the
原因权利全部在本地完成，可能永远不会有两个客户
reason rights are all done locally may
never have two clients never have to
等待，有很多并行性，因为您知道此分片服务器用于
wait there's a lot of parallelism
because you know this shard server for a
如果是碎片的话，衬衫可以独立地提供更多的机会
and the shirts are for a more
opportunity independently if the shard
一个正确的服务器，您知道它必须将其数据推送到相应的
server for a gets right you know it has
to push its data to the corresponding
分片服务器和其他数据中心，但可以执行这些推送
shard servers and other data centers but
it can do those push pushes
独立于其他分片服务推送，因此在
independently of other shard service
pushes so there's parallelism both in
如果稍微考虑一下，就可以提供服务并推动写作
serving and and pushing the writes
around if you think about it a little
一点是，这种设计实际上也实际上有利于阅读和阅读
bit it's this design also essentially
effectively favors reads and the reads
尽管这样做确实不会对本地数据中心产生任何影响。
really never have any impact beyond the
local data center the rights though do a
只要您做对了一点工作，您就知道客户不必等待
bit of work whenever you do a right you
know the client doesn't have to wait for
它，但分片服务器随后必须将权限推给其他数据中心
it but the shard server then has to push
the rights out to the other data centers
而且您知道这意味着另一个数据中心的新数据将继续进行
and you know means that new data the
other data center then proceed very
速度很快，因此阅读所涉及的工作少于权利，这对阅读而言是适当的
quickly so reads involve less work than
rights and that's appropriate for a read
繁重的工作量，如果您更担心速率性能，可以想象
heavy workload if you are more worried
about rate performance you could imagine
例如其他设计，您可以想象其中实际读取的设计
other designs for example you can
imagine design in which reads actually
必须咨询多个数据中心，并且权限完全是本地的，因此您可以
have to consult multiple data centers
and rights are purely local so you can
想象一个方案，当您执行读取操作时，您实际上会读取数据
imagine a scheme in which you have when
you do a read you actually read the data
从其他每个日期开始，从每个日期获取所需密钥的当前副本
from each of the other date the current
copy of the key you want from each of
其他数据中心，然后选择最新的数据中心
the other data centers and choose the
one that's most recent perhaps and then
权利很便宜，品种很贵，或者您可以想象
rights are very cheap and breeds are
expensive or you can imagine
这两种策略的组合采用某种法定人数重叠方案，或者
combinations of these two strategies
some sort of quorum overlap scheme or
您写多数，只在多数数据时写多数
you write a majority and write a
majority at the only a majority of data
中心和满足大多数数据中心的需求，并依靠重叠和
centers and meet a majority of data
centers and rely on the overlap and in
实际上，人们有真实的实时系统用于商业用途
fact there are real live systems that
people use in commercially in real
遵循这种设计的网站，因此，如果您对真正的
websites that follow much this design so
if you're interested in sort of a real
的世界版本，您可以查找亚马逊的发电机系统或开放式
world version of this you can look up
Amazon's dynamo system or the open
源码Kassandra系统
source
Kassandra system
比我在这里草拟草图时要详细得多，但他们会遵循
there was much more elaborated than when
I've sketched out here but they follow
相同的基本模式，所以这种方案的通常名称是最终的
the same basic pattern so the usual name
for this kind of scheme is eventual
一致性，其原因是至少在开始时
consistency and the reason for that is
that at least initially if you do a
向其他读者和其他数据中心写信不能保证EC或正确
write other readers and other data
centers are not guaranteed EC or right
但他们总有一天会因为您要推广权利，所以他们会
but they will someday because you're
pushing out the rights so they'll
最终会看到您的数据，因此无法保证订购，因此例如
eventually see your data there's no
guarantee about order so for example if
我是客户，我写他从他们开始，然后我写钥匙
I'm a client and I write he's starting
with them and then I write a key
从确定您知道M发出开始，这就是我获得篮圈碎片的权利
starting with a sure you know M sends
out it's my right to shards of a rim
发出一项权利，服务器发出a发出我的权利，但是您知道
sends out one right and the server for a
sends out my right for a but you know
这些可能会在广域以不同的速度或不同的路线传播
these may travel at different speeds or
different routes on the wide area
网络，也许我写了，也许客户首先写了他们，然后写了一个，但是
network and maybe I wrote maybe the
client wrote em first and then a but
也许如果他们先到达，然后更新为上午，也许我
maybe if they for a arrives first and
then the update for am and maybe I
以相反的顺序到达另一个数据中心，因此不同的客户端
arrive at the opposite order at the
other datacenter so different clients
会按照不同的顺序观察更新，所以您知道没有顺序
are gonna observe updates in different
orders so there's you know no order
保证
guarantee
从某种意义上说，最终意义的最终一致性是
the sense the sort of ultimate meaning
eventual consistency is that if things
安顿下来，人们停止写作，所有这些最终写出消息
settle down and people stop writing and
all of these write messages finally
到达他们的目的地已处理，然后我最终
arrive at their destinations are
processed then I'm an eventually an
最终一致的系统应该最终以所有存储的相同值结束
eventually consistent system ought to
end up with the same value stored at all
最终所有复制品的意义
of the all of the replicas that's the
sense of which it's eventually
如果您等待尘埃落定，您将得到
consistent if you wait for the dust to
settle you're gonna end up with
每个人都有相同的数据，这是一个很弱的规范，这是一个非常
everybody having the same data and
that's a pretty weak spec that's a very
规格较弱，但您知道，因为规格较宽松，因此有很大的自由度
weak spec but you know because it's a
loose spec there's a lot of freedom in
实施和很多机会来获得良好的绩效
the implementation and a lot of
opportunities to get good performance
因为该系统基本上不需要您立即执行任何操作或
because the system basically doesn't
require you to instantly do anything or
遵守任何排序规则，这与大多数一致性大不相同
to observe any ordering rules it's quite
different from most of the consistency
到目前为止，我们再次提到的方案已在已部署的系统中使用
schemes we've seen so far again as I
mentioned it's used in deployed systems
最终的一致性是很不错的，但对于应用程序程序员来说却很难
eventual consistency is but it can be
quite tricky for application programmers
因此，让我画出一个您可能想在网络上做的事的例子
so let me sketch out a an example of
something you might want to do in a web
还有您必须非常小心的网站，您可能会感到惊讶
and the website where you would have to
be pretty careful you might be surprised
如果这是最终的一致性应用程序示例，假设我们正在构建一个网站
if this is an eventual consistency app
example suppose we're building a website
存储照片，每个用户都有一组您知道的照片存储为
that stores photos and every user has a
you know set of photo photos stored as
您知道具有某种唯一ID的键值对是键，每个用户
you know key value pairs with some sort
of unique ID is the key and every user
有一份清单，其中包含一份允许其他人使用的公开照片清单
has a list of maintains a list of their
public photos that they allow other
人们看到这样的假设，我拍了张照片，然后将其插入
people to see so supposing I take a
photograph and I want to insert it into
该系统，或者您知道我与Web服务器联系，然后Web服务器运行
this system or you know I human contact
the web server and the web server runs
代码将我的照片插入存储系统，然后添加一个
code that's gonna insert my photo into
the storage system and then add a
引用我的照片到我的照片列表，所以也许
reference to my photo to my photo list
so maybe
运行，也许会发生这种情况，我们会说它发生在客户端c1（即网络）上
run maybe this happens we'll say it
happens on clients c1 which is the web
我正在与之交谈的服务器，但是代码看起来好像有一个代码调用
server I'm talking to and maybe but the
code looks like is there's a code calls
我的照片的放置操作，这真的应该引起您的注意
the put operation for my photo
and it really should be a keen about you
我只是求职者而已，因此我将我的照片和
I'm just gonna candidates just a few
plus value so I insert my photograph and
然后当这个放置完成时，II将照片添加到我的列表中
then when this put finishes then I I add
the photo to my list
对，这就是我的客户代码看起来像别人在看的东西
right that's what my my clients code
looks like somebody else is looking at
我的照片看上去松散地看起来是我的照片列表的副本，然后
my photographs loosely gonna look fetch
a copy of my list of photos and then
他们将查看列表中的照片，以便客户致电
they're gonna look at the photos that
are on the list so client to maybe calls
获取我的列表，然后向下查看列表，然后呼叫获取该照片
get for my list and then looks down the
list and then calls get on that photo
也许他们看到我刚刚上传的照片在列表中
maybe they see the photo I just uploaded
it on the list
他们会为那张照片的你知道的钥匙做的，是的，所以这
and they're gonna do a get it for the
you know key for that photo yeah so this
就像完全简单的代码看起来应该可以工作，但是
is like totally straightforward code
looks like it ought to work but in an
最终保持一致的系统并不一定要正常工作，
eventually consistent system it's not
necessarily going to work and the
问题是，即使客户在这样一个
problem is that these two puts even
though the client did them in such an
明显的顺序是先插入照片，然后将对该照片的引用添加到我的照片中
obvious order first insert the photo and
then add a reference to that photo to my
照片列表，事实是，在这种情况下，
list of photos the fact is that in this
event early consistent scheme that I
概述了第二个放置点可能会在第一个放置点之前到达其他数据中心
outlined this second put could arrive at
other data centers before the first put
因此，如果另一个客户端正在其他数据中心进行读取，则可能会看到
so this other client if it's reading at
a different data center might see the
更新列表，其中包含我的新照片，但当其他客户和其他数据出现时
updated list with my new photo in it but
when that other client and another data
中心去获取列表中的照片，该照片可能尚不存在
center goes to fetch the photo that's in
the list this photo may not exist yet
因为优先权未必会超过客户的妻子
because the first right may not have
arrived over the wife of the client
周二是这样，如果这只是例行公事，
Tuesday's so if this is just gonna be
routine occurrence in an eventually
一致的系统，如果我们不考虑这种更聪明的事情
consistent system if we don't sort of
think of anything more clever this kind
在某种程度上看起来像是代码失效的行为
of behavior where it sort of looks like
the code out of work you know at some
直观的水平，但是当您实际去阅读该系统的规格时，
intuitive level but when you actually go
and read the spec for the system which
就是说不能保证你意识到啊，你知道这显然是正确的
is to say no guarantees you realize that
ah you know this obviously this correct
看代码可能完全不行，我想它将要做的是
looking code may totally not do it I
think it's going to do these are often
称为异常和
called anomalies and
您知道思考的方式并不一定就是您的这种行为
you know the way to think about it is
not necessarily that this behavior you
知道您在列表中看到了第三名，但照片不存在但还不存在
know you saw the list third on a list
but the photo didn't exist yet it's not
一个错误，它不是不正确的，因为毕竟系统永远无法保证
an error it's not incorrect because
after all the system never guaranteed
这种食物会做，实际上会在这里产生照片，所以
that this food was gonna do that it's
gonna actually yield the photo here so
不是因为它不正确，而是因为它比您可能要弱
it's not that it's incorrect it's just
that it's weaker than you might have
希望这样，仍然有可能对这样的系统进行编程，而人们会全力以赴
hoped so it's still possible to program
such a system and people do it all the
时间，并且有很多技巧可以使用，例如，您知道
time and there's a whole lot of tricks
you can use for example you know a
防御性程序员可能会观察到程序员可能会编写代码
defensive programmer might observe
programmer might might write code
很清楚，如果您说我的意思是列出它可能还不存在
knowing that well if you say something I
mean list it may not really exist yet
因此，如果您在列表中看到对某张照片的引用，则会得到一张
and so if you see a reference to a photo
in the list you get a photograph that's
不在那里，您只是重试，请稍等一下，然后重试，因为by by by
not there you just retry just wait a
little bit and retry because by and by
照片可能会显示出来，如果不显示，我们将跳过它，不要
the photo will probably show up and if
it doesn't we'll just skip it and don't
向用户显示它，因此完全可以用这种样式进行编程，但是我们
display it to the user so it's totally
possible to program in this style but we
绝对可以希望存储系统的行为更加直观
could definitely hope for behavior from
the storage system that's more intuitive
比这会使程序员撒谎的生活更容易
than this that would make the
programmers lie life easier sort of we
可以想象系统异常少然后是非常简单
could imagine systems that have fewer
anomalies then yes very simple
最终保持一致的系统还可以，然后再继续讨论如何
eventually consistent system okay before
I go on to talking about how to maybe
使一致性更好一点我想讨论一些重要的事情
make the consistency a little bit better
I want to discuss something important I
忽略了当前的最终一致性系统，这就是如何
left out about this current eventual
consistency system and that's how to
决定最近的权利，以便对某些数据（如果有的话）
decide on which right is most recent so
for some data if data might ever be
由不止一个政党撰写，我们可能不得不
written by more than one party there's
the possibility that we might have to
确定哪个数据项是较新的，所以假设我们有一些密钥或可以调用
decide which data item is newer so
suppose we have some key or call okay
以及它的权利，您知道客户启动K的速率，因此当客户写时
and to rights for it you know to clients
launch rates for K so when client writes
一个值另一个客户写一个值两个，我们需要建立一个系统
a value one another client writes a
value of two we need to set up a system
这样所有三个数据中心都同意密钥K的最终值是什么，因为
so that all three data centers agree on
what the final value of key K is because
毕竟，我们至少要保证最终的一致性。
after all we're at least guaranteeing
eventual consistency when the dust
结算所有数据中心都具有相同的数据，所以您知道数据中心
settles all the data centers all have
the same data so you know data center
三个将获得这两项权利，并将其中一项作为最后一项
three is gonna get these two rights and
it's gonna pick one of them as the final
当然是um数据中心对K的价值-看到相同的权利
value for K well of course um datacenter
- sees the same rights right it sees its
拥有自己的权利，所以他们都看到这对组合破裂，而且他们最好都做出
own right so they're all seeing this
pair breaks and they all had better make
同样的决定，无论哪一个都是最终值，以及
the same decision about which one that'd
be the final value regardless and the
命令他们到达正确的位置，因为我们不知道您知道数据中心
order that they arrived in right because
we don't know you know the data center
三个可能会观察到这些以一种顺序到达，而另一些数据中心可能会
three may observe these to arrive in one
order and some other data center may
观察他们以不同的顺序到达我们不能只接受第二个
observe them to arrive in a different
order we can't just accept the second
一个，并使其成为最终值，满足更强大的决策方案
one and have that be the final value
meet a more robust scheme for deciding
钥匙的最新最终价格是多少，所以我们需要一些
what the final the most recent value is
for a key so we're gonna need some
版本号的概念和最简单的版本签名方法
notion of version numbers and the the
most straightforward way to sign version
数字是使用挂钟时间，所以为什么不使用挂钟时间和想法
numbers is to use the wall clock time so
so why not wall clock time and the idea
是当客户端生成分片服务器或分片服务器时，
is that when a what a client generates a
put either it or the shard server the
本地图表服务器正在与之交谈的对象将查看当前时间，哦，您知道它是
local chart server talks to will look at
the current time oh it's you know it's
现在是125，它将把那个时间与版本号相关联
125 right now and it'll sort of
associate that time as a version number
在密钥的版本上，然后我们注释这些写消息
on its version of the key so then we'd
annotate these these write messages
这些实际上都将时间戳存储在数据库中并注释这些写入
these actually both store the timestamp
in the database and annotate these write
数据中心之间随时间发送的消息，所以您可能知道这是
messages sent between data centers with
the time so you know maybe this one was
在102处签发，此权利在103发生
written at 102 and this right occurred
at 103
因此，如果102位作家或假设三个权利之一先到达，则
and so if if 102 writer or suppose the
one of three right arrives first then
数据中心三将把该密钥和时间戳一放入数据库
the data center three will put in its
database this key and the timestamp one
两三，当102的权利到达时
two three
and when the right for 102 arrives the
标准中心会说，哦，那实际上是我的一项较早的权利
standard Center will say oh actually
that's an older right I'm just gonna
忽略此权限，因为它具有较低的时间戳和时间步长
ignore this right because it has a lower
timestamp and the time step I already
有，当然，如果他们到达，而另一个命令做了一个句子，我们会
have and of course if they arrive and
the other order did a sentence we would
实际上已经短暂存储了此权限，直到具有较高权限的权限为止
have actually stored this right briefly
until the right with the higher
时间戳到了，但是它将取代它，因为每个人都看到
timestamp arrived but then it would
replace it I mean since everybody sees
至少有一些时间戳，你知道他们什么时候终于收到所有
it some time stamps at least you know
when they finally receive whatever all
这些互联网上的好消息都会以
these great messages over the Internet
they're all gonna end up with the
具有最高编号值的数据库可以，所以这几乎可以工作，并且
databases that have the highest numbered
values okay so this almost works and
有两个，它有两个小问题，一个是两个数据中心
there's two there's two little problems
with it one is that the two data centers
如果他们确实同时写，可能实际上分配了这个小时间戳
if they do writes at the same time may
actually assign this little time stamp
这是相对容易解决的，通常的方式是时间
this is relatively easy to solve and the
way it's typically done is the time
邮票实际上是时间对或其他东西，而高位本质上
stamps are actually pairs of time or
whatever and the High bits essentially
只要某种标识符，实际上只要是
hand some sort of identifier could
actually be almost anything as long as
它是唯一的某种标识符，例如数据中心名称或ID等
it's unique some sort of identifier like
the data center name or ID or something
在低位只是为了引起来自不同数据中心的所有管道标志或
in the low bits just to cause all pipe
signs from different data centers or
您想要的不同服务器，然后如果两个权限相同
different servers to be you want and
then if two rights ride with the same
来自不同数据中心的时间会有不同的低位
time in them from different data centers
are gonna have different low bits and
这些一点将用于消除歧义的两个说
these little bits will be used to
disambiguate which of the two right says
是较低的时间戳，因此应与
is the lower timestamp and therefore
should yield to the other with the
更高，好吧，我们要在底部位粘贴一些ID，
higher okay so we're gonna stick some
sort of ID in the bottom bits and the
论文实际上谈到了这样做，这是很常见的，另一个问题是
paper actually talks about doing this
it's very common the other problem is
如果所有数据中心都完全正确，则该系统可以正常工作
that this system works okay if all of
the data centers are exactly
时间同步，这是扳手论文强调的
synchronized in time and this is
something a spanner paper stressed a
长度很大，所以如果所有数据中心都同意所有服务器上的时钟
great length so if the clocks on all the
servers that all the data centers agree
这会没事的，但是如果时钟按秒关闭或
and this is gonna this is gonna be okay
but if the clocks are off by seconds or
也许只有几分钟，然后我们在这里遇到了一个严重问题
maybe even minutes then we have a
serious problem here one not so
重要的问题是，您早知道的权利
important problem is that rights that
come earlier in time you know that
应该被较晚的权利覆盖，所以可能是较早的权利
should be overwritten by later right so
it could be the rights that came earlier
实时是因为时钟被分配了高时间戳，并且
in real time are because the clocks are
on are assigned high time stamps and
因此不会被后来出现的权利所取代
therefore not superseded by rights that
came later in time now we never made any
关于此ID的最终保证，我们从没说过哦，权利
guarantees about this ID eventual
consistency and we never said oh rights
稍后，我们仍将正确地赢得客户
that come later in time we're gonna win
over rightfully the clients nevertheless
我们不想已经足够弱的一致性，我们不想拥有它
we don't want to be already weak enough
consistency we don't want to have it
有不必要的奇怪行为，例如用户，真的很好
have needlessly
strange behavior like users really well
注意到他们在吃东西，然后稍后更新似乎并不需要
notice they eat something and then they
updated later doesn't seem to take
效果，因为先前的更新被分配了两次，认为它太大
effect because the earlier update was
assigned two times thinks it's too large
此外，如果某些服务器时钟太高，这不对，您是否知道
in addition if some servers clock is too
high and it doesn't right you know if
核心小组说快一分钟，然后当我们没有其他人的时候将一整分钟
it's caucus say a minute fast then it'll
be a whole minute when no other we have
等待所有服务想法赶上最新的快速服务器
to wait for all the service thoughts to
catch up to the minute fast servers
在其他人可以写有关热量的时钟之前解决这个问题
clock before anybody else can do the
write about heat in order to solve that
问题解决此问题的一种方法是称为Lamport的时钟
problem one way to solve that problem is
this idea called Lamport clocks the
论文谈论了这一点，尽管论文并未真正说出
paper talks about this
although the paper doesn't really say
他们为什么使用灯或时钟，我猜至少是因为
why they use the lamp or clocks I'm
guessing it's at least partially for the
我只是不介意Flambeau时钟是Wade分配的时间
reason I just I don't mind
Flambeau clock is Wade assigned time
与实时相关的邮票，但希望在某些情况下会出现此问题
stamps that are related to real time but
which hope would this problem at some
服务器的时钟运行速度太快，因此每个服务器都保持其价值
servers having clocks that are running
too fast so every server keeps a value
称为这个T max，这是迄今为止看来最高的版本号
called this T max which is the highest
version number it seems so far from
其他任何地方
anywhere else so
因此，如果其他人正在生成您提前知道的时间戳
so if somebody else is generating
timestamps that are you know ahead of
实时您知道其他服务器可以看到其团队轴将使用的时间戳
real-time you know the other servers to
see this timestamps their team axes will
反映在实时之前，然后在服务器需要分配时间戳时
reflect ahead of real time and then when
a server needs to assign a timestamp of
版本号转换为新版本的方式是：
version number to a new put the way it
will do that is it'll take the max of
这个团队的斧头加一个和墙上的时钟时间
this team ax plus one and the wall clock
time
实时，这意味着新的版本号，所以这是版本
the real-time so that means that new
version number so this is the version
文丘里一致性系统中值所需的数字
numbers that we need to accompany the
values in our venturi consistent system
因此每个新版本号都将高于最高版本
so each new version number is going to
be higher than the highest version
看到的数字比最后一个礼仪的数字高得多
number seen so higher than whatever the
last Rite was for example to the data
我们正在更新并且至少与实时一样高，所以如果没有人的时钟在
that we're updating and at least as high
as real-time so if nobody's clock is
在此Tmax之前加一个实际上可能比实时时间小，
ahead this Tmax plus one will probably
actually be smaller than real time and
如果某些服务器有一个疯狂的时钟，则时间戳工具会实时结束
the time stamp tool end up in real time
if some server has a crazy clock that's
太快了，那么将导致所有其他服务器全部更新
too fast then that will cause all other
servers all the ones it's updates
推进团队坐标轴，以便他们分配的新版本号高于
advanced the team axes so that when they
allocate new version numbers higher than
他们从服务器上看到的任何女士评分的版本号
the version number of whatever ladies
rate they saw from the server whose
时钟太快了，所以这是兰伯特时钟，这就是论文的方式
clock is too fast okay so this is
Lampert clocks and this is how the paper
分配版本号总是在分布式系统中出现
assigns version numbers come up all the
time in distributed systems alright so
我想提出关于我们最终一致的系统的另一个问题是
another problem I want to bring up about
our eventually consistent system is the
关于如何对同一键的并发速率进行实际处理的问题
problem of what to do about concurrent
rates to the same key it's actually even
更糟的是，同时发生的利率可能同时承担的可能性
worse the possibility that concurrent
rates might carry might both carry
应该保留的重要信息，以便考试双方的客户
important information that ought to be
preserved so for exam a client of both
这两个您是否知道不同的客户，一个客户和一个客户-他们
did both of these you know different
clients client one and client - they
都发布相同的密钥
both issue a put to the same key
这两个都让我们将其发送到数据中心3的问题是
and both of these let's get sent it to
datacenter 3 the question is what's a
数据中心3处理这里的信息，这是一个
data center 3 do about the information
here and the information here this is a
真正的难题实际上没有一个好的答案
real puzzle actually there's not a good
answer
该论文使用的是最后的Raider胜利，即他是数据中心3
the what the paper uses is the last
Raider wins that is datacenter 3 he's
看一下这里签名的版本号
gonna look at the version number that is
signed here and the version number is
在此处分配的其中一个数据中心ID会稍晚一些
assigned here one of them will be higher
slightly later in time data center ID
再高一点或者我是数据中心3
and a little bit higher or something I'm
a datacenter 3 you will simply throw
删除具有较低时间戳的数据，并接受具有较高时间戳的数据
away the data with the lower timestamp
and accept the data with the higher
裤子上印有印章的东西，就这样，它就使用了最后的Raider取胜策略，
pants that stampin and that's it so it's
using this last Raider wins policy and
因为它具有确定性，每个人都会得到的优点
in that has the virtue that it's
deterministic and everybody's gonna get
相同的答案，您可以想到的例子就是人，所以您
the same answer you can think of
examples in which it's people so you
知道例如假设这些看跌期权试图做的是增加a
know for example supposing what these
puts are trying to do is increment a
因此，这些客户都看到了他们都拥有的价值10的柜台附近
counter so these clients both saw near
the counter with value 10 they both had
一个，也许我们已经把11正确了，但是您知道我们真正想做的是
one and maybe we've put 11 right and but
you know what we really wanted to do is
让他们都增加计数器的值12
have them both increment the counter and
have it had value 12
所以在这种情况下，最后的攻略胜利并不是我们真正的伟大
so in that case last Raider wins is
really not that great what we really
本来希望数据中心3将这种增量与
would have wanted was for datacenter 3
to sort of combine this increment and
该增量最终为12，所以您知道这些系统确实
that increment end up with the value of
12 so you know these systems are really
通常足够强大，可以做到这一点，但我们希望我们能真正做到更好
generally powerful enough to do that but
we would like better what we'd really
像是更复杂的冲突解决方案
like is more sophisticated conflict
resolution
您以及我们看到的其他系统的方式
you
and the way other systems we've seen saw
这是支持真实交易的最强大的系统，因此代替
this the most powerful system to support
real transactions so instead of instead
刚放入get的过程实际上具有执行原子操作的增量运算符
of just having put in get it actually
has increment operators that do atomic
交易增量增量没有丢失，这有点像
transactional increments increments
weren't lost and that's sort of a
交易可能是解决冲突的最强大方法
transactions of maybe the most powerful
way of doing resolving conflicting
更新我们还看到了一些支持mini概念的系统
updates we've also seen some systems
that support a notion of mini
至少在单个数据上您可以拥有原子的交易
transactions where at least on a single
piece of data you can have atomic
原子增量或原子测试和设置等操作，您也可以想象
operations like atomic increment or
atomic test and set you can also imagine
想要有一个确实可以解决自定义冲突的系统
wanting to have a system that does come
sort of custom conflict resolution so
暴露我们保留在这里的这个价值是您所知道的一个购物车
exposing this value that we're keeping
here is a shopping cart you know with a
一堆项目，我们的用户可能因为他们正在运行，所以您知道两个
bunch of items in it and our user may
because they're running you know two
风浏览器中的Windows窗口将两个不同的项添加到它们的窗口中
windows in the wind browser
adds two different items to their
来自两个不同Web服务器的购物车
shopping cart from two different web
servers
我们希望这两个相互冲突的写入同一个购物车来解决
we'd like these two conflicting writes
to the same shopping cart to resolve
可能是通过将两个购物车和球固定在一起而不是
probably by taking set union of the two
shopping carts and ball instead of
扔掉一个并接受另一个我正在提出
throwing one away and accepting the
other I'm bringing this up
令人满意的解决方案的确，该论文并没有提出太多建议
satisfying solution indeed the paper
doesn't really propose much of a
解决方案，这只是每周保持一致的系统的一个缺点，很容易获得
solution it's just a drawback of weekly
consistent systems that it's easy to get
您可能对相同的数据拥有冲突的权利
into a situation where you might have
conflicting rights to the same data that
您想拥有针对特定应用的复杂解决方案
you would like to have sophisticated
sort of application specific resolution
但这很难，而且就像人们的荆棘一样
to but it's generally quite hard and
it's just like a thorn in people's sides
通常必须忍受，最终
that has to be lived with typically and
that that goes for both the eventual
一致，我的稻草人在这里为P和P与纸舞之手
consistency my straw man here hand for
the and for the P versus the paper dance
和几个段落，它可以用来做得更好
and a couple of paragraphs it it could
be used to do better
他们并没有真正探索这一点，因为很难回到最终状态
they don't really explore that because
it's difficult okay back to eventual
如果你还记得我的稻草人系统有一个真正的问题，甚至连
consistency my straw man system if you
recall it had a real problem with even
非常简单，这非常简单，我知道我们确实放了一张照片并放了一张照片
very simple this very simple scenario I
know we did put a photo and put a photo
列出，然后其他人有所不同，它会读取新的，但是
list and then somebody else in a
difference and it reads the new this but
当他们阅读照片时，发现那里什么也没有，所以我们可以做
when they read the photo they find
there's nothing there so can we do
更好地建立一个系统，它仍然允许本地读取和本地
better can we build a system of it's
still allows local reads and local
权利，但有一点小教训，托马斯，我要提出一个
rights but is has slightly mini-lesson
Thomas I'm going to propose one that's
使我更接近论文，这是稻草人
strong me into this kind of one step
closer to papers so this is straw man
太
too
在这个方案中，我要提出一个新的
and
in this scheme I'm gonna propose a new
运算符不仅可以放置和获取，还可以是客户可以使用的接收器运算符，
operator not just put and get but also a
sink operator that clients can use and
接收器操作员将执行的操作将是键，版本号以及接收器
the sink operator will do will be the
key and a version number and what sink
当客户端调用它为接收器时执行操作，直到所有数据中心的副本
does when a client calls it is sink
waits until all data centers copies of
键K至少是最新的指定版本号，因此这是一种方法
key K are at least up to date as of the
specified version number so it's a way
客户可以说我要等待的命令我也要等所有人知道
of forcing order the client can say look
I'm gonna wait as well everybody knows
关于这个价值，我只想看看每一件事都是中心
about this value and I wanna only see
after every one everything is Center
知道此值，以便客户知道要使用的版本号
knows about this value and in order for
clients to know what version numbers to
为了通过接收器，我们将稍微改变看跌期权的调用，以便您说出看跌期权的钥匙
to pass the sink we're gonna change the
put call a bit so that you say put key
value和put返回您可以调用的此更新的K的版本号
value and put returns the version number
of the of this updated K you could call
这个下沉的人问演戏是一种障碍，我们可以
this this sink is asking that acting is
a sort of a barrier offense we could
称之为最终一致性加
call this eventual consistency plus
障碍见呼唤障碍
barriers see calls the barrier
我会在稍后向用户介绍如何操作，但请记住这一点
I'm gonna talk about how to users in a
moment but just keep in mind this thing
呼叫可能会非常慢，因为它的自然实现是
calls likely to be pretty slow because
the natural implementation of it is that
它实际上熄灭了，并与所有其他数据中心进行了对话，并要求他们
it actually goes out and talks to all
the other data centers and asked them
您知道是您的密钥支付版本，至少您知道此版本号
you know is your version of key pay up
to at least you know this version number
然后必须等待展位等待数据中心做出响应，如果有的话
and then have to wait booth for the data
centers to respond and if any of them
说不，是的，然后必须读取该数据，是的，那么您将如何使用它
say no it's got to then read that data
yes all right so how would you use this
再说一遍，现在我们的照片列表也许是正在更新的客户
well again for our photo list
now maybe client one that's updating
它将被调用的照片插入将要获得版本的照片
photos it's going to call put to insert
the photo it's gonna get a version
现在您知道程序员必须拥有的编号，这里存在更新的危险
number now you know the programmer now
has to there's a danger here that update
这张照片，但是您知道如果您知道的其他数据中心还没有出现怎么办
the photo this but you know what if some
other data center you know hasn't seen
我的照片还没有，所以程序员会说“同步”，而你会沉没
my photo yet so then the programmer is
gonna say sync and you're gonna sink the
照片等待所有数据中心使用该版本号返回的版本号
photo wait for all data centers to have
that version number that was returned by
放置，并且只有在同步返回之后，客户端一次调用放置更新才会更新
put and only after the sync return will
client one call put update update the
照片列表，现在如果客户2出现，我必须阅读照片列表并
photo list and now if client two comes
along I must read the photo list and
然后在照片中，你知道谁知道客户二将做
then to be in the photo you know who
knows client two is going to do a get of
照片列表，假设时间流逝对他们来说是一样的
the photo list let's say time is
passing the same for them it's gonna do
获取照片列表，如果看到该列表中的照片，它将获取
a get at the photo list and if it sees
the photo on that list it'll do a get
您再次在照片的本地数据中心知道了，现在我们实际上在
you know again in its local data center
of the photo and now we're actually in
如果客户在其他数据中心看到照片，情况会好得多
much better situation if client to in a
different data center saw the photo in
则表示该客户希望已经调用此列表
this list then that means that client
want had already called put on this list
因为如果客户需要的话，就是这个清单添加了清单的素材
because it's this put that adds the
footage of the list if client wanted
已经被称为“放到此列表中”，这意味着客户现在已经给出了方法
already called put on this list that
means the client one now given the way
此代码正常工作，已经调用过接收器，接收器直到
this code works right had already called
sink and sink doesn't return until the
照片出现在所有数据中心，这意味着客户端两个可以
photo is present at all data centers so
that means that client two can the
客户二的程序员可以很好地依赖列表中的照片，这意味着
programmer for client two can rely on
well the photos in the list that means
这个将镜头添加到列表中的人，他们的同步已完成，并且事实
this whoever added the footage to the
list their sync completed and the fact
完成此操作意味着照片随处可见，并且
that this thing completed means the
photo is present everywhere and
因此，我们可以依靠此获取照片实际返回照片，这样
therefore we can rely on this get photo
actually returning the photograph ok so
这行得通，而且实际上相当实用，确实需要相当小心
this works and it's actually reasonably
practical it does require fairly careful
在您所知道的程序或程序员方面已经思考过了
thought on the part of the program or
the programmer you know has to think aha
我在这里需要一个水槽，我需要放一个水槽以使工作正常
I need a sink here I need to put sink
put in order for things to work out
对读者来说，读者的速度要快得多，但读者仍然需要
right the reader for the readers much
faster but the reader still needs to
想想，您知道我至少要测试一下程序员对您的要求
think oh you know I'm gonna at least
tested that the programmer has to you
知道检查一下是否他是程序员是否做了一个获取列表，然后我
know check with it if he's if the
programmer does a get list and then I
从该列表中获取照片，您知道吗，请验证代码是否正确
get photo from that list that uh you
know verify that indeed the code
在为列表添加一些东西之前修改了名为接收器的列表
modified the list called sink before
adding some things for list that is
相当多的想法
quite a bit of thought
这与接收器有关，因为所有与执行命令有关，请确保
with this is all about the sink cause
all about is enforcing order make sure
在读者发生这种事情之前完全完成
that this completely finishes before
this happens the readers so that sink
对于作家来说，明确的强制秩序也是读者必须考虑的问题。
and sort of explicitly forces order for
writers readers also have to think about
顺序在本示例中，顺序实际上是显而易见的，但是如果
order the order is actually obvious in
this example but it is true that if the
作家确实放了一个看跌期权，然后下沉，然后放了第二件事，然后几乎总是
writer did put a put then sink and then
put of a second thing then almost always
读者需要阅读第二件事，然后阅读第一件事，因为
readers need to read the second thing
and then read the first thing because
保证您从此沉没方案中摆脱出来这些障碍是
guarantees you get out of this out of
this sink scheme these barriers is that
如果读者看到第二条数据，那么他们一定也会看到
if a reader sees the second piece of
data then they're guaranteed to also see
第一块数据，这意味着读者需要成为第二块
the first piece of data so that means
the reader sort of need to be the second
首先是数据，然后是第一项数据，所以有一个
piece of data first and then and then
the first item of data okay so there's a
关于容错的问题主要在于一个数据中心是否发生故障
there's a question about fault tolerance
mainly at if one data center goes down
这意味着接收器会阻塞，直到其他数据中心启动
that means the sink blocks until the
other data centers brought up
那是绝对正确的，所以您完全正确，这是一个不是
that's absolutely right so you're
totally correct this is a this is not a
好办法，这在警察下沉的路上有点像个稻草人
great scheme alright this is sort of a
straw man on the way the cops this sink
被称为会阻止这种方式的人们
called would block the way this actually
that sort of version of this that people
在现实世界中使用以避免此问题，您是否知道任何数据
use in the real world to avoid this
problem will you know whatever data
居中向下将永远阻止水槽堵塞
centers down will the sink block forever
is that puts and gets both actually
请咨询数据中心的法定人数，以便此接收器仅在等待您知道
consult a quorum of data center so that
this a sink will only wait for you know
说大多数数据中心承认他们拥有最新的
say a majority year of data centers to
acknowledge that they have the latest
照片的版本及其获取实际上必须参考重叠部分
version of the photo and it get will
actually have to consult an overlapping
大多数数据中心为了获取数据所以事情并不是真的
majority of data centers to in order to
get the data so things are not really
真实版本可能不像我可能再次暗示的那样乐观
real versions of this are not perhaps as
rosy aasaiya as I may be implying again
以这种方式工作的系统就是您感兴趣的发电机
the the systems that work in this way is
you're interested it's dynamo
和卡桑德拉（Cassandra），他们使用法定人数来避免壁谈。
and Cassandra and they use quorums to
avoid the wall talks pop okay okay so
这是一个简单的设计，尽管速度很慢，但语义也很不错
this is a straightforward design and has
decent semantics even though it's slow
而且正如您所观察到的那样，容错性能不是很好
and this as you observe not very fault
tolerant the read performance is
出色的，因为至少在我们达到法定人数的情况下，读取仍然是本地的
outstanding because the reads are still
for local at least if we if the quorum
设置是一次读取所有写入，写入性能虽然不是很好，但是
setup is read one write all and the
write performance is not great but it's
好吧，如果您写得不是很多，或者您不介意等待很长时间，
okay if you don't write very much or if
you don't mind great waiting and the
为什么您可以说服自己利率表现是
reason why you can maybe convince
yourself that the rate performance is
不是灾难，毕竟Facebook memcache D论文必须发送
not a disaster is that after all the
Facebook memcache D paper has to send
通过主数据中心拥有所有权利，是的，您知道Facebook在运行
all rights through the primary data
center so yeah you know Facebook runs
多个数据中心和客户都与他们交谈，但是费率却要
multiple data centers and clients talk
to all of them but the rates have to all
被发送到一个主要数据中心的我的续集数据库中
be sent to the my sequel databases at
the one primary data center
同样，扳手写入必须等待大多数副本站点才能完成
similarly spanner writes have to wait
for a majority of replica sites to
在客户认为继续进行之前先确认权利，因此这一概念
acknowledge the rights before the
clients thought to proceed so the notion
客户可能会裁定，权利可能必须等待与之交谈
that clients might have dis rule that
the rights might have to wait to talk to
其他数据中心为了使读取速度更快，似乎没有
other data centers in order to allow the
reads to be fast is does not appear to
在实践中还是很暴行的妈妈我仍然知道你可能还是想
be outrageous in practice mom still I
you know you might like to nevertheless
有一个比这更好的系统，以某种方式具有同步的语义
have a system that does better than this
to somehow have semantics of sync that
某种程度或同步性正在迫使这一投放肯定在所有人看来都在发生
sort of or sync is forcing this put
definitely appears to everyone to happen
在第二次投放之前，您可能希望拥有而无需花费任何费用，因此我们将
before the second put you might like to
have that and without the cost so we'll
对系统感兴趣，这已经开始接近警察的工作
be interested in systems and this is
starting to get close to what cops does
对那些不是强迫客户等待的系统感兴趣的系统
interested in systems in which instead
of sort of forcing the clients to wait
在这一点上，我们以某种方式将订单编码为一条信息，
at this point we somehow just encode the
order as a piece of information that
我们将告诉读者或告诉其他数据中心和一个简单的
we're going to tell the readers or tell
the other data centers and a simple
本文提到的不可扩展的实现是
do that which the paper mentions as a
non scalable implementation is that at
每个数据中心，所以这是每个数据中心的日志记录方法，而不是
each data center so this is a logging
approach at each data center instead of
让不同的分片服务器在其他数据中与对方通信
having the different shard servers talk
to their counterparts in other data
服务器有点独立，而不是每天我们都会在中心
servers sort of independently instead at
every day the center we're gonna have a
指定的日志服务器，负责向其发送写操作
designated log server that's in charge
of communicating of sending writes to
另一个数据中心，这意味着如果客户正确执行了操作，则将其置于
the other data center so that means if a
client does it right does it put to its
本地分片，而不是仅发送数据的图表
local shard and that's chart that shard
instead of just sending that the data
与其他数据中心分开，将与他的本地日志对话
out sort of separately to the other data
centers will talk to his local log
服务器，并将权限附加到该数据中心所在的一个日志中
server and append the right to the one
log that this data center is
积累，然后如果客户说对另一个密钥进行写操作，也许
accumulating and then if a client say
does a write to a different key maybe
我们在这里写密钥a和密钥b，而不是再次写shard
we're writing key a and key B here
instead of again instead of this shard
服务器独立地发送密钥B的权利，它将告诉
server sending the right to key B sort
of independently it's gonna tell the
本地日志服务器将权限附加到日志，然后日志服务器发送出去
local log server to append the right to
the log and then the log server send out
将其日志按日志顺序发送到其他数据中心，以便所有数据中心
their log to the other data centers in
log order so that all data centers are
保证会看到第一次诉讼的权利，他们将希望能够处理该比率
guaranteed to see the right to a first
and they're gonna hope process that rate
首先，然后所有数据中心都将看到我们拥有B的权利，
to a first and then all data centers are
going to see our right to B and that
意味着如果客户首先拥有权利，然后又有权成为
means if a client does a right to a
first and then does it right to be the
写入将以该顺序显示，并在其日志a和b中显示，并且将被发送
writes will show up in that order and it
in its log a and B and they'll be sent
首先拥有t的数据权，然后拥有t的每个数据中心的权利
the right to a first and then the right
to be to each of the t's data centers
并且实际上可能必须将它们发送到某种单一日志接收中
and they probably actually have to be
sent to a kind of single log receiving
服务器以日志顺序到达时一次播放一个速率，因此
server which plays out the rates one at
a time as they arrive in log order so
如果论文批评，这就是采伐策略
this is the logging strategy if the
paper criticizes
它实际上重新获得了我们想要的一些性能，因为现在客户
it's actually regain some of the
performance we want because now clients
我们不再是现在，我们消除了客户可以回去的汇
we're no longer we now eliminate the
sinks the clients can go back to this
先放a然后放B，他们的客户看跌期权可以在
going put of a and then put B and they
client puts can return as soon as the
数据位于本地日志服务器上的日志中，因此现在客户端放置和获取
data is sitting in the log at the local
log server so now client puts and gets
现在又很快了，但我们保留的排序方式是
are now quite fast again
but we're preserving order sort of by
基本上是通过条目和日志的序号，而不是
basically through the sequence numbers
of the entries and the logs rather than
通过让客户等待，这很好，我们得到了您现在知道的订单，
by having the clients wait so that's
nice we get the order you know now we're
强制执行有序的写操作，我们使权利按顺序显示在
forcing ordered writes and we're causing
the rights to show up in order at the
其他数据中心，以便阅读客户可以按顺序看到它们，等等
other data center so that reading
clients will see them in order and so
我们的示例应用程序实际上可以使用此方案解决它们
our my example application might
actually work them out with this scheme
本文指出的这种解决方案风格的缺点是
the drawback that the paper points to
about this style of solution is that the
现在，日志服务器的所有权利都必须通过此一台日志服务器，因此，如果我们
log server now all the rights have to go
through this one log server and so if we
有一个很大的大型数据库，可能有数百台服务器至少在
have a big big database with maybe
hundreds of servers serving at least in
总共有相当高的工作量正确的工作量，所有权利
total a reasonably high workload the
right workload all the rights have to go
通过此日志服务器，可能所有权限都必须通过
through this log server and possibly all
the rights have to be played out through
远端有一台接收日志服务器，而一台日志服务器作为
a single receiving log server at the far
end and a single log server as the
系统不断增长，单个日志服务器可能停止运行的碎片越来越多
system grows there get to be more and
more shards a single log server may stop
足够快地处理所有这些比率，因此警察不遵守此规定
being fast enough to process all these
rates and so cops does not follow this
将订单约束传达给其他数据中心的方法
approach to conveying the order
constraints to other data centers
好吧，所以我们要建立一个至少可以从客户角度出发的系统
okay so we want to build a system that
can at least from the clients point of
查看处理速度并纯粹在本地读取，我们不想等待
view process rates and reads purely
locally we don't want to have to wait
您不希望客户等待以获得订单，我们想要我们喜欢的货代
you don't want clients to wait in order
to get order we want a forward we like
这些速率正在异步转发的事实，但我们不知何故
the fact that these rates are being
forward asynchronously but we somehow
想消除中央日志服务器，所以我们想以某种方式传达
want to eliminate the central log server
so we want to somehow convey
向其他数据中心订购信息，而不必考虑所有费用
order information to other data centers
without having to funnel all our rates
通过一个原木好吧，现在让我们了解实际的警察
through a single logs alright so now
that brings us to what cops is actually
到现在为止，当我可以谈论的时候，开始是警察的职责和职责
up to so when I can talk about now is
starting to be what cops does and what
我说的是警察的非GTE版本
I'm talking about though is the non GTE
version of cops cops without get
交易很好，所以警察是这里的基本策略是当警察客户
transactions ok so the cops is the basic
strategy here is that when cops clients
在本地读写，它们积累有关顺序的信息
read and write locally they accumulate
information about the order in which
他们所做的事情比日志记录方案要精细一些
they're doing things that's a little
more fine-grain than the logging scheme
并且只要有客户，该信息就会发送到远程数据中心
and that information is sent to the
remote data centers whenever a client
没有引用，因此我们拥有客户端上下文的概念，并且作为客户端
doesn't quote so this we have this
notion of client context and as a client
确实得到一些看跌期权，您可能知道一个客户获得了X，然后得到了Y
does get some puts you know maybe a
client as a get of X and then I get it Y
然后有一些价值的Z看跌期权
and then a put of Z with some value
客户端用来实现Budhan get的库正在运行
the context the library that the client
uses that implements Budhan get is going
在这种情况下，作为沙堆放在一边
to be accumulated in this context
information on the side as the put sand
会发生，因此如果客户端无法获得，则版本会产生一些价值
gets occur so if a client doesn't get
and that yields some value with version
2我将保存为例，也许get返回当前
2 I'm just going to save that as an
example maybe get returns the current
x的值，以及当前版本2的当前值，也许Y返回
value of x and that current value House
version 2 and maybe Y returns the
版本在上下文中要累积的当前值
current value of version for what's
going to be accumulated in the context
是该客户端已读取X并获得了版本2，然后在获取之后了解为什么
is that this client has read X and a got
version 2 then after the get for why the
警察客户端库将添加到上下文中，以便不仅仅是我们已经阅读过
cops client libraries gonna add to the
context so that it's not just we've read
X并获得版本2，但现在我们已经阅读Y并获得版本4，
X and gotten version 2 but also now
we've read Y and gotten version 4 and
当客户做一个把发送到本地的信息
when the client does a put the
information that's sent to the local
分片服务器不只是放置密钥，如果值是，还这些
shard server is not just put key and
what if the value is but also these
依赖关系，所以我们将告诉Z的本地分片服务器
dependencies so we're going to tell the
local shard server for Z that this
客户在执行看跌期权X之前已经阅读并获得版本2和Y
client has already read before doing the
put X and got version 2 and Y and got
版本4
version 4
而且您知道这里发生的是我们告诉客户在哪里
and you know what's going on here is
that we're telling where the client is
表示客户现在拥有的此订购信息
expressing this ordering information
that this put to Z now the client had
在做脚之前，似乎是X版本2和Y版本4
seemed X version 2 and Y version 4
before doing the foot so anybody else
读过Z版本的人最好还是和野兽一起看X＆Y
who reads this version of Z had also
better be seeing X&Y with the Beasties
版本，如果客户随后又做了其他操作，则类似地说Q
versions and similarly if the client
then does a put of something else say Q
发送到本地分片服务器的不仅是Q，
what's going to be sent to the local
shard server is not just the Q and this
而且这个客户以前做过的事实也得到了输入，所以让我们
but also the fact that this client had
previously done some gets input so let's
假设此看跌期权产生版本3，您知道本地分片服务器说
suppose this put yields version 3 you
know the local shard server says a high
将版本3分配给Z的新值，然后当我们退出时
assigned version three to your new value
for Z then when we come to do the quit
Q的内容将伴随着依赖信息，该信息表示
of Q is going to be accompanied with
dependency information that says this
放置在此Q放置在创建Z的Z放置之后
put comes after this put of Q comes
after the put of Z that created Z
第三版，至少在概念上其余部分
version three and at least notionally
the rest of the context
还应该通过，尽管出于各种原因我们会看到警察
ought to be passed as well although
we'll see that for various reasons cops
可以优化此信息，如果有处理权，则仅发送
can optimize away this information and
if there's a proceeding put only sends
要点的版本信息，所以问题对
the version information for the point so
the question is is it important for the
命令的上下文我不相信，所以我认为我认为治疗就足够了
context to be ordered I don't believe so
I think I think it's sufficient to treat
上下文或至少在看跌期权中发送的信息只是一个大袋子
the context or at least the information
that's sent in the put as just a big bag
至少有四个非交易警察的依存关系，所以
of dependencies for at least four
non-transactional cops okay so the
客户是这个上下文的社区，并且基本上每次发送时都发送上下文
clients are community this context and
basically send the context with each put
上下文正在编码此订单信息，这在我之前的稻草中
and the context is encoding this order
information that in my previous straw
稻草人2被水槽强迫而不是那样做，我们不是
man straw man 2 was sort of forced by
sink instead of doing that we're not
等待伴随着这些看跌期权，哦，这个看跌期权需要在这些之后
waiting for accompanying these puts with
oh this put needs to come after these
先前的值，而这个看跌期权需要在这些先前的值警察之后
previous values and this put needs to
come after these previous values cops
称这些关系需要在之前的这些之后
calls these relationships that this put
needs to come after these previous
依赖值
values of dependency
和依赖关系，并将其写为假设这只脚产生了Z版本
and dependency and it writes it as
supposing this foot produces Z version
三个我们表示为真的，实际上有两个依赖关系，一个在这里
three we express it as really there's
two actually two dependencies here one
是X版本2在Z版本3之前，另一个是Y
is that X version two comes before Z
version three and the other is that Y
版本4出现在Z版本3之前，而这仅仅是定义
version four comes before Z version
three and these are it's just definition
或本文用来谈论这些个别订单的注释
or notation that the paper uses to talk
about these individual pieces of order
警察需要执行的信息还可以，那么这是什么
information that cops needs to enforce
alright so so then what is this what is
这个依赖信息传递给本地分片服务器，那是什么
this dependency information this passed
to the local shard server what does that
实际导致警察做得很好，当它收到来自
actually cause cops to do well eats cops
shard server when it receives a put from
本地客户端首先分配新版本号，然后存储新版本号
a local client first it assigns the new
version number then it stores the new
您知道的值会为Z存储此新值以及该版本号
value you know it stores for Z this new
value along with the version number that
它分配的长版本号，然后将整个混乱发送给每个
it long version number that allocated
and then it sends the whole mess to each
另一个数据中心的数据，因此至少有一些非GT应对本地分片服务器
of the other data center so at least
some non GT cops the local shard server
只记住键值，而最新版本号实际上不记得
only remembers the key value and latest
version number doesn't actually remember
依赖关系，并且仅将它们通过网络转发给其他数据
the dependencies and only forwards them
across the network to the other data
中心，所以现在的位置是，假设我们有一个客户
centers so now the position were in is
that let's say we had a client produced
Z的看跌期权和一些值，它被分配了版本号v3，并且具有
a put of Z and some value it was
assigned version number v3 and it had
这些依赖
these dependencies
XV 2 + YB 4对，这是从数据中心1发送的，比如说
XV 2 + a YB 4 right and this is sent
from datacenter 1 let's say to the other
数据中心，所以我们有一个数据中心2和数据中心3现在都收到了
data center so we got a datacenter 2 and
datacenter 3 both receive this now in
实际上，此信息是从The Shard服务器发送给ze的，所以有很多
fact this information is sent from The
Shard server for ze so there's lots of
分片服务器，但仅涉及Z的分片
shard servers but only the shard for Z
is involved in this
所以这里数据中心3的衬衫是Z的，这是从发送来的。
so here datacenter 3 the shirts are for
Z is going to receive this put from sent
由客户端短服务器转发
by the client short server forwards it
这个短服务器具有您知道XV的此依赖项信息
this short server the the with this
dependency information that you know X V
2和Y在出现在ZB 3之前，但这实际上意味着在操作上是
2 and Y before come before Z B 3 but
that really means is operationally is
直到Z的新版本才能向客户公开
that this new version of Z can't be
revealed to clients until its
依赖关系，这些版本的x和y已经在
dependencies these versions of x and y
have already been revealed to clients in
数据中心3，这意味着分片服务器visi必须拥有此权限
datacenter 3 so that means that the
shard server visi must hold this right
必须延迟将此权限应用于Z，直到知道这2个依赖项
must delay applying this right to Z
until it knows that these 2 dependencies
在本地数据中心中可见，这意味着Z必须关闭
are visible in the local data center so
that means that Z has to go off let's
说您知道我们为X提供这些分片服务器，而短裤则为Y
say the you know we have these shard
server for X and the shorts are for Y
Z的实际上必须向X的分片服务器和分片服务器发送消息
Z's gotta actually send a message to the
shard server for X and the shard server
Y表示您知道当前版本的版本号是多少
for Y saying you know what's the version
number for a current version for a
x和y的数字，如果这两个分片都必须等待结果
number for x and y and has to wait for
the result if both of these shards
服务器说哦，您知道他们给出的版本号是2或更高或4
servers say oh you know they give a
version number that's 2 or higher or 4
或Y更高，则Z可以继续并将其应用于本地数据表
or higher for Y then Z can go ahead and
apply to put to its local table of data
但是您知道这两个分片服务器可能尚未收到更新
however you know maybe these two shard
servers haven't received the updates
对应于Y的外向版本2，而KC必须
that correspond to version 2 of
extraversion for Y and that KC has to
坚持这个更新，分片服务器必须坚持这个更新，并且
hold on to this update the shard server
is he has to hold on to this update and
告诉所指示的X或Y版本
tell
the indicated versions of X or Y ever
实际到达并安装在这两个短服务器上，因此可能
actually arrived and been installed on
these two short servers so there may be
现在并且只有在数据中心3看到这些依赖关系之后才有一些延迟
some delays now and only after these
dependencies are visible at datacenter 3
只有这样，a4z的碎片才能继续运行，并为Z编写更新的稳定值
only then can the shards of a4z go ahead
and write updated stable for Z to have
版本3好的，这当然意味着，如果客户
version 3 ok and what's what that means
of course is that if a client the
数据中心3会读取Z，然后看到版本3，因为他已经在等待
datacenter 3 does a read for Z and sees
version 3 then because he already waited
这意味着如果该客户端随后读取X或Y，则可以确保至少看到
that means if that client then reads X
or Y it's guaranteed to see at least
X的版本2和Y的至少版本2，因为他没有显示碎片或
version 2 of X and at least version 2 of
Y because he didn't reveal the shards or
直到确定依赖项可见之后才显示Z
didn't reveal Z until it was sure the
dependencies would be visible ok so
问题，如果x和y可能由于网络而永远无法获得其值怎么办
question what if x and y never get their
values perhaps due to a network
永远用Z碎片块进行分区，是的，而语义要求Z
partition with the Z shard block forever
yeah the um the semantics require the Z
永远阻止碎片是绝对正确的，所以您肯定有一个
shard to block forever that's absolutely
true so you know there's certainly an
假设在这里，他们就是您，您可能会知道两种可能的结果
assumption here that well they're you
know two ways that that might turn out
好吧，有人修理网络或修理任何损坏的东西，x和
ok one is somebody repairs the network
or repairs whatever was broken and x and
y最终确实获得了更新，这是解决此问题的一种方法，然后z将
y do eventually get their updates that
be one way to fix this and then z will
最终能够应用更新可能需要等待很长时间
finally be able to apply the update
might have to wait a long time the other
可能是数据中心被完全破坏了
possibility is maybe the data center is
entirely destroyed
你的意思是建筑物烧毁了，所以我们根本不必担心
you mean the building burns down and so
we don't have to worry about this at all
但这确实指出了一个对因果一致性和
but it does point out a problem that's
real criticism of causal consistency and
那就是这些延误实际上是很讨厌的，因为你可以想象哦
that's that these delays can actually be
quite nasty because you can imagine oh
您知道Z正在等待X的正确值到达，即使
you know Z is waiting for the correct
value for X to arrive you know even if
没有失败，没有任何消耗，即使仅仅是缓慢也可以
there's no failures and nothing burns
down even mere slowness can be
令人讨厌的Z伙伴，您必须等待X良好显示，可能是X具有
irritating Z mate you have to wait for X
to show up well it could be that X has
已经出现并到达此图表
already showed up and has arrived at
this charts
但它本身可能依赖于键a，因此此图表服务器无法
but it itself had dependencies maybe on
key a and so this chart server can't
安装它直到更新更新为止，因为X的X取决于X
install it until the update for a
arrives because X this put of X depended
在某个键a上，Z仍然需要等待，因为Z等待的是
on some key a and Z still has to wait
for that because what Z's waiting for is
为了使该版本的X对客户端可见，因此必须安装它，以便
for this version of X to be visible to
client so it has to be installed so if
如果X的更新已到达但它本身正在等待一些更新，则到达
it's arrived if the update for X is
arrived but itself is waiting for some
其他依赖性，那么我们可能会得到这些级联的依赖性
other dependency then we may get these
cascading dependency Waits and in real
生活实际上这些，你知道这些可能会发生，这是其中之一
life actually these you know these
probably would happen and it's one of
人们提出的问题以及您知道反对来电的问题是一致性
the problems that people bring up and
you know against calls are consistency
当您尝试说服他们时，最好是这个层叠的问题
when when you try to persuade them it's
a good idea this problem of cascading
延迟，所以这太糟糕了，尽管在这一点上确实是
delays so that's too bad um although on
that note it is true that the authors of
警察文件对P的关注实际上有几个有趣的地方
the cops paper have a follow on P
actually a couple of interesting
后续论文，但其中之一对这种级联有一定的缓解作用
follow-on papers but one of them has
some mitigations for this cascading
体重问题还可以，所以对于一个照片示例，这是该警察的方案
weight problem okay so for a photo
example this is the scheme this cop
方案实际上将解决我们的照片示例，原因是您知道
scheme will actually solve our photo
example and the reason is that you know
我们正在谈论的这个投放是照片列表的投放，依赖项是
this put we're talking about is the put
for the photo list the dependencies is
将要拥有的依赖列表是照片的插入，这意味着
gonna have and its dependency list is
the insert of the photo and that means
当威利斯的照片的推杆到达远程站点时，
that when the put for the photo Willis
arrives at the remote site the remote
chard服务器本质上将等待插入照片，然后
chard server is essentially going to
wait for the photo to be inserted and
在更新照片列表之前可见，因此远程站点中的任何客户端
visible before it updates the photo list
so any client in a remote site that is
能够看到更新后的照片列表中的新照片，因此能够
able to see the new photo of the updated
photo list is guaranteed to be able to
还可以查看照片，因此此COP方案可以修复照片和照片列表示例
see the photo as well so this cop scheme
fixes the photo and photo list example
警察实施的方案通常称为因果一致性
this the scheme the cops is implementing
is is usually called causal consistency
所以有一个问题是由程序员来指定依赖项
so there's a question is it's off to the
programmer to specify the dependencies
不，事实证明，尽管该上下文信息此上下文信息
no it turns out that though that context
information this context information
在这里积累，警察客户库可以自动积累
that's accumulated here the cops client
library can accumulate it automatically
因此该程序仅会获取和放入，甚至可能不需要查看版本
so the program only does gets and puts
and may not even need to see the version
数字如此简单的程序，我们只是做得到输入和内部警察
numbers so simple program we just do
gets inputs and internally the cops
库维护这些上下文并将这些额外信息添加到put
library maintains these contexts and
adds this extra information to the put
我们的个人电脑，以便程序员只是得到一些推杆和系统
our pcs so that the programmer just just
does get some puts and system kind of
自动跟踪依赖项信息，因此非常方便
automatically tracks the dependency
information so that's very convenient I
就是说，您知道，您会弹出一个级别，了解我们现在已经建立了一个系统
mean just a you know pop up a level for
a moment you know we now built a system
那就是语义足够强大，可以制作照片示例代码
that's that is as semantics powerful
enough to make the photo example code
正确地进行锻炼以使其具有预期的结果，而不是
work out correctly to have it sort of
had the expected result instead of
结果异常，至少可以说它相当有效，因为没有人
anomalous results and at least arguably
it's reasonably efficient because nobody
您是否知道客户永远不必等待权限完成就可以了
was you know the client never has to
wait for rights to complete there's none
该沉没业务的一部分，而且沟通大多是独立的
of this sink business and also the
communication is mostly independent
没有中央日志服务器，因此可以说两者都相当高
there's no central log server so
arguably this is both reasonably high
性能并具有合理的语义和合理的一致性，因此
performance and has reasonably good
semantics reasonably good consistency so
这种设计产生的一致性通常称为因果关系
the the consistency that this design
produces is usually called causal
一致性，实际上这是比本文提出的要早得多的想法
consistency and it's actually a much
older idea than this paper there's been
一堆电话，所以本文之前的一致性方案确实是一堆
a bunch of call so consistency schemes
before this paper indeed a bunch of
后续工作，这是一个让人非常喜欢的治疗想法
follow-on work so it's a treating idea
that people like a lot
因果一致性是什么意思，在这里我提出
what causal consistency is what it sort
of means and here I am putting up I
从纸上想出图二的副本
think a copy of figure two from the
paper
定义说的是客户行为引起的
the sort of what the definition says is
that the clients actions induce
依赖关系，因此有两种方法可以诱导依赖关系，一种是
dependencies so there's two ways that
dependencies are induced one is if a
给定客户有一个看跌期权，然后我得到它得到，然后是PUD或看跌期权
given client there's a put and then I
get does it get and then a PUD or a put
然后看跌期权，然后我们说看跌期权取决于前一个看跌期权或获得
and then a put then we say that the the
put depends on the previous put or get
因此，在这种情况下，为什么要放两个是否取决于一个的X的放置，那就是
so that in this case put of why if two
depends on the put of X of one so that's
一种形式的依赖关系另一种形式的依赖关系，如果一个客户释放了一个
one form of dependency another form of
dependency if is if one client frees a
从存储系统中获取价值，然后我们说，获得那一秒
value out of the storage system then we
say that that the get that that second
客户端发出的取决于实际插入的相应认沽期权
client issued depends on the
corresponding put that actually inserted
来自先前客户的价值，此外，我们还说
the value from a previous client and
furthermore we say that the dependency
关系是可传递的，因此您知道此投放取决于获得此
relationship is transitive so that you
know this put depends on that get this
由客户二获得取决于客户一的认沽权和
get by client two depends on the put by
client one and by transitivity in
此外，我们可以得出结论，委托人的礼物取决于委托人的礼物
addition we can conclude that the client
two's get depends on client ones gift
因此，这意味着例如客户三的最后一次看盘取决于
and so that means that this last put of
by client three for example depends on
所有这些先前的操作，所以这是因果相关性的定义
all of these previous operations so
that's a definition of causal dependency
然后因果一致的系统说，如果通过
and then a causally consistent system
says that says that if through the
依赖性的定义我刚刚概述了a取决于B对不起B取决于a和
definition of dependency I just outlined
a depends on B sorry B depends on a and
客户端读取B，则客户端随后还必须看到依赖项
a client reads B then the client must
subsequently also see a the dependency
因此，如果客户查看了两个有序操作中的第二个操作
so if client ever sees through a second
of two ordered operations operations
通过依存关系排序，然后客户端也保证
ordered by dependency and the client is
also then after that guaranteed to be
能够看到该操作所依赖的一切
able to see the everything that that
operation depended
你知道，这就是定义，从某种意义上来说，你知道
you know so that's the definition and
it's you know in a sense kind of
直接来自系统实际执行的操作，因此当
directly derived from what the system
actually does so this is very nice when
更新是因果相关的，即如果您知道这些客户端，并且在某些情况下
updates are causally related that is if
yeah you know these clients and in some
感觉他们正在通过存储间接认识彼此
sense they're talking to each other you
know indirectly through the storage
系统，所以客户很喜欢我，如果有人
system and so the clients are I kind of
wear that of you know if we somebody
读取此值，c5看到五个，并检查您知道的代码
reads this value and c5 sees five and
inspects the code you know they can
得出结论，真的，您真的知道这存在某种意义
conclude that really really you know
this there's a sense in which this put
肯定是在最后一次下注之前已经来了，所以如果您看到斜线但您
definitely must have come before this
last put and so if you see slash but you
真的很不错，您真的应该看到这个第一眼，所以在这种意义上
really gosh you really just deserve to
see this first put so in that sense
因果一致性为您提供了这种程序员的良好体验
causal consistency gives you this
programmers kind of a sort of well
行为良好的签证使他们能够看到良好的行为价值
behaved visas allows them to see well
behave values coming out of the storage
系统因果一致性的另一个好处是，当它
system another thing that's good about
causal consistency is that when it
当系统中的两个值不是两个时更新不是因果的
updates when two values in the system
are not two updates are not causally
有关因果一致性系统，您知道警察存储系统没有
related the causal consistency system
you know the cops storage system has no
义务是关于维持非因果关系的更新之间的顺序
obligation is about maintaining order
between updates that are not causally
相关，例如，如果我的意思是对性能有好处，那么例如，如果我们
related so for example if I mean that's
good for performance so example if we
你知道委托人做一个X的交易，然后我放Z，然后围绕
have you know client one does a put of X
and then I put Z and then around the
同时客户二对为什么会有一个你知道没有因果关系
same time client two does a put of why
there's a you know there's no causal
这些之间的关系，因此您知道对不起没有因果关系
relationship between these and therefore
you know sorry there's no causal
Y的看跌期权与委托人的任何行动之间的关系等
relationship between the put of Y and
any of the actions of client one and so
警察可以完全完成与Y的推杆相关的所有工作
the cops is allowed to do all the work
associated with the put of Y completely
对于客户而言，是独立投放的，而播放的方式是完成了
independently for client ones puts and
the way that plays out is that it's done
而Y的投放则完全发生在
and the put of Y is sort of entirely
happens in the servers that for the
为什么这两个puts只涉及分片服务器
shard of why these two puts
are only involve servers for the shards
X和Z在其中可能需要进行一些交互，因为远程
that X and Z are in it may require some
interaction here because the remote
Z的服务器可能不得不等待此放置时间到达，但不必
servers for Z may have to wait for this
put to arrive not but they don't have to
与负责Y的服务器进行通讯，如果在某种意义上
talk to the servers that are in charge
of of Y so if that's a sense in which
因果一致性允许良好，允许并行性和良好的性能，并且您
causal consistency allows good allows
parallelism and good performance and you
知道这与像Anna这样的线性化系统可能不同
know this is different from potentially
from linearizable systems like Anna
可线性化的系统，这个Y实际位于X的真实位置之后
linearizable system the fact that this
put Y came after the put of X in real
时间实际上对线性化存储系统有一些要求，但
time actually imposes some requirements
on the linearizable storage system but
这里没有因果一致性的此类要求，因此您可能会
there's no such requirements here for
causal consistency and so you might be
能够建立因果一致性因果一致的系统，速度更快
able to build a causal consistency
causally consistent system that's faster
比线性化系统还好，还有一个问题是警察会获得更多收益
than a linearizable system okay there's
a question would cops gain any more
通过将信息放入客户端上下文中就可以了，所以这可能是
information by including puts in the
client context okay so it's this may be
是今天的演讲问题的参考，所以我为什么不
a reference to the today's lecture
question it is the case so why don't I
如果客户确实得到XI，则说明电子问题的答案
意思是看它的上下文可能得到X，然后放到Y，然后放一个
mean look at its context does the get of
X maybe and then put to Y and then a
在上下文中退出Z最初是X版本，您知道当我们
quit to Z in the context initially is X
version something you know that when we
客户，因为服务器的放置将包括此上下文
client since the puts of the server it's
gonna include this context along with it
但在实际系统中，存在这种优化
but in the actual system there's this
optimization that after a put the
上下文被替换为put的版本号和任何
context is replaced by simply the
version number for the put and any
上下文中的先前内容（即有关X的信息是
previous stuff in the context like
namely this information about X is a
来自客户上下文的竞争，因此仅包含
race from the from the clients context
so it only includes after put the
上下文只是替换为从put返回的数字，因此
context is just replaced with
number returned from the put that so
这不是返回吗，您知道为什么的第七版以及为什么
isn't this returns you know version
version seven of why and the reason why
这是正确的，不会因非交易而丢失任何信息
this is correct and doesn't lose any
information for the non-transactional
为此，当把这个看跌期权发送到所有远程站点时，
cops is that for this when this put is
sent out to all the remote sites the put
附带了X版本，无论在依赖项列表中是什么，因此不会放置
is accompanied by X version whatever in
the dependency list so this put won't be
直到所有X都被应用为止
applied until at all and each data
center until this X is also applied so
然后，如果客户随后将其正确处理，则将其发送给客户
then when if the client then does this
put right what this turns into is sent
到其他数据中心的确是Z值和一些依赖项的看跌期权
to other data centers is really a put
with Z and some value and the dependency
只是Y版本，其他所有数据中心都将等待
is just Y version seven all the other
data centers are going to wait for
他们将在应用Z之前进行检查他们将检查Y版本7
they're gonna check before applying Z
they're gonna check that Y version seven
已经在他们的数据中心应用了，我们知道Y版本7不会
has been applied at their data center
well we know the Y version seven won't
可以在其数据中心应用，直到提供X版本为止
be applied at their data center until X
version whatever is supplied at that
数据中心，所以这里存在级联延迟
data center so there's sort of a
cascading delays here where that is
告诉其他数据中心等待安装Y版本7意味着
telling other data centers to wait for Y
version seven to be installed implies
他们还必须已经在等待7依赖的Y版本
that they must also already be waiting
for whatever Y version seven depended on
因此，我们不需要同时包含X版本，X版本和
and because of that we don't need to
also include X version the X version and
此依赖项列表，因为这些数据中心已经在等待它
this dependency list because those data
centers will already be waiting for it
那个版本的X，所以答案是没有警察叫
that version of X so the answer the
question is no cops call the
非交易警察不需要有任何东西不需要记住
non-transactional cops doesn't need to
have anything doesn't need to remember
完成后放入上下文中
the gets in the context after it's done
put
好的，关于该方案的最后一件事要注意的是，警察只能看到
all right a final thing to note about
this scheme is that cops only see
某些关系只有它知道某些因果关系
certain relationships it's only aware of
certain causal relationships that is it
只有您知道警察知道，如果单个客户端线程执行放置操作，然后
only you know cops is aware that if a
single client thread does a put and then
您知道警察记录的另一个看跌期权客户，因此第二个看跌期权取决于
another put client you know cops record
so this the second put depends on the
第一本书还让警察知道，哦，客户阅读了什么
first book furthermore cops is aware
that oh what a client does a read of a
取决于我的确定性价值，是创造价值的依据
certain value that it's depending on I'm
the one to put the created that value
因此，取决于任何依赖的东西，所以你知道警察是
and therefore depending on anything that
that depended on so you know cops is
在这里直接知道这些依赖关系，但是通常
directly aware of these dependencies
here however it could it is often the
通过更广泛的渠道传达因果关系的案例
case that causality in the larger sense
is conveyed through channels that cops
并不知道，例如，您知道客户是否做了X的看跌期权，然后
is not aware of so for example you know
if client one does a put of X and then
您所知道的控制客户的人会呼叫客户
the human you know who's controlling
client one calls up client to on the
电话，还是您知道电子邮件，或者说您知道我只是
telephone or it's you know email or
something that says look you know I just
用一些新信息更新了数据库，为什么不看一下
updated the database with some new
information why don't you go look at it
对，然后您知道的客户从更大的意义上讲得到了X
right and then client to you know does
it get of X sort of in a larger sense
您是否知道因果关系暗示客户确实应该
causality would you know
suggest the client to really ought to
看到更新的X，因为客户端从X过去的电话中获得了新的
see the updated X because client to new
from the telephone call that X had been
更新，所以如果警察知道电话，它将有
updated and so if cops had known about
the telephone call it would have
实际包括，如果
actually included the it would have
actually caused the extra sorry if the
电话本身就是看跌期权，你知道那应该是看跌期权
telephone call had been itself a put
right you know it would have been a put
的电话在这里，我得到的电话在这里，如果得到
of telephone call here and I get of
telephone call here and if this get had
看到推特警察会知道足够的知识来安排这个获得会看到那个推特
seen that put cops would know enough to
arrange that this get would see that put
但是因为警察完全不知道电话，所以没有理由
but because cops was totally unaware of
the telephone call there's no reason to
期望这个收益会实际产生看跌期权的价值，所以警察有点
expect that this get would actually
yield the put value so cops is sort of
强制因果一致性，但仅针对来源而言
enforcing causal consistency but only
for the sources the kinds of causation
警察是直接意识到的，这意味着警察的意义是
the cops is directly aware of and that
means that the sense in which cops is
因果一致性可以很好地消除异常行为
causal consistency sort of eliminates
anomalous behavior well it only
如果将因果关系的概念限制在以下范围，则可以消除异常行为
eliminates anomalous behavior if you
restrict your notion of causality to
从什么意义上说警察会看到它，您仍然会看到奇怪的行为
what cops can see it in the larger sense
you're going to still see odd behavior
您肯定会看到某些情况，您知道有人相信
you definitely going to see situations
where you know someone believes that a
值已更新，但他们看不到更新的值，这是因为
values been updated and yet they do not
see the updated value that's because
他们的信仰是由警察不了解的事情引起的
their belief was caused by something
that cops wasn't aware of all right
我不会谈论的另一个潜在问题是，记住
another potential problem which I'm not
gonna talk about is that the remember
对于带有照片列表的照片示例，有一个特定的顺序
for the photo example with the photo
list there was a particular order of the
添加照片以及查看照片的特定顺序
adding a photo and that particular
different order of looking at photos
因为我们绝对依赖
that made the system work with causal
consistency as we're definitely relying
如果读者阅读了照片列表，然后阅读了
on the there being sort of if the reader
reads the photo list and then reads the
按照照片引用的顺序排列照片
photo in that order that the fact that a
photos refer
乔安娜（Joana）图片列表意味着可以成功读取照片，但是
joana photo list means that the read of
the photo will succeed it is however the
在某些情况下，没有一个阅读顺序或
case that there are situations where no
one order of reading or combination of
阅读或写作的顺序将导致我们想要的行为，并且
orders of reading or writing will cause
sort of the behavior we want and that
但这导致了我没有足够的时间进行交易
but this is leading into transactions
which I'm not gonna have time enough to
解释一下，但至少我想提一下本文设置的问题
explain but at least I want to mention
the problems the paper set up so
假设我们有照片列表，并且受访问控制列表保护
supposing we have our photo list and
it's protected by an access control list
和访问控制，这基本上是允许使用的用户名列表
and an access control this is basically
a list of usernames that are allowed to
看看我列表上的照片，是否意味着该软件
look at the photos on my list
does that means that the software that
通过访问控制实现这些照片列表，这需要您
implements these photo lists with access
control this needs to be able to you
知道阅读列表，然后阅读访问控制列表，看看用户是否
know read the list and then read the
access control list and see if the user
尝试进行读取的操作在访问控制列表中，但是顺序都不行
trying to do the read is in the access
control list and however neither order
获取访问控制列表和照片列表的过程，因此，如果
of getting the access control list and
the list of photos works out so if the
客户端代码首先获取访问控制列表，然后获取以下列表：
client code first gets the access
control list and then gets the list of
实际上，订购的照片并不总是能很好地工作，因为
photos that order actually doesn't
always work so well because supposing my
客户端Reesie访问控制列表，看到我在列表中，但是随后
client Reesie access control list and
sees that I'm on the list but then right
在这里，此照片的所有者将我从访问控制列表中删除
here the owner of this photo this
deletes me from the access control list
并插入一张我不应该在列表中看到的新照片
and inserts a new photograph that I'm
not supposed to see in the list list
对，所以c2做了一个，您知道访问控制的端口是要删除我，然后
right so c2 does a you know a port of
access control is to delete me and then
放入照片列表以添加照片，然后我的客户将无法看到
a put of the photo list to add a photo
I'm not allowed to see then my client
绕到第二个得到它看到此列表，您可能会看到此列表是
gets around to the second get it sees
this list you may see this list which is
现在更新的列表中有我不允许看到的照片，但我
the now the updated list that has the
photo I'm not allowed to see but my
客户认为aha我在访问控制列表中，因为它正在读取旧的
client thinks aha I'm in the access
control list because it's reading an old
一
one
这是这张照片，所以我可以看到你，在这种情况下，你知道我们
and here's this photo so I'm allowed to
see you so in that case you know we're
得到不一致的组合，我们知道这是一种不一致的组合
getting an inconsistent what we know to
be an inconsistent sort of combination
一个新列表和一个旧的访问控制列表，但实际上除了
of a new list and an old access control
list but there was really nothing but
但是因果一致性可以做到这一点，它称之为一致性只能说得很好
but causal consistency allows this it'll
it calls a consistency only says well
每次您都会看到至少与依赖项一样新的数据
you're gonna see data that's at least as
new as the dependencies every time you
做到这一点，确实，如论文所指出的那样，如果您认为
do a get so and indeed if you know as
the paper points out if you think it
阅读客户首先阅读以下内容的列表也不正确：
through it's also not correct for the
reading client to first read the list of
照片，然后阅读访问控制，因为在此之间潜行
photos and then read the access control
this because sneaking in between this
虽然这可能是我阅读的这张照片可能有我不允许的照片
though this might have a this that I
read may have a photo I'm not allowed to
看到，那时也许访问控制不包括我，但是在
see and at that time maybe the access
control this didn't include me but at
这时列表的所有者可能会删除私人照片，将我添加到
this point the owner of the list may
delete the private photo add me to the
访问控制列表，然后我可能会在列表中看到自己
access control list and then I may see
myself in the list so again if we do it
按照这个顺序也不正确，因为我们可能会看到我们可能会变旧
in this order it's also not right
because we might see we might get an old
列表和新的访问控制列表，以确保因果关系的一致性
list and a new access control list so
causal consistency as I've described it
到目前为止，还不足以处理这种情况，您知道我们需要
so far isn't powerful enough to deal
with this situation you know we need
能够获得相互一致的列表和访问权限的一些概念
some notion of being able to get a
mutually consistent list and access
控制列表通过某种形式在更新之前或之后进行
control lists through either sort of
both before some update or both after
警察GT实际上提供了一种方法
and cops GT actually provides a way of
doing this it by essentially doing both
加兹，但警察GT发送了全套
Gatz
but but cops GT sends the full set of
依赖关系会在客户端无法获取时返回给客户端，这意味着
dependencies back to the client when it
doesn't get and that means that the
客户端提交可以实际检查两者的依赖关系
client is submit is in a position to
actually check the dependencies of both
这些返回值中，看到啊哈，您知道列表存在依赖性
of these return values and see that aha
you know there's a dependency for list
这是这些版本的抱歉，因为可能存在依赖关系
that is a version of these sorry for
that there might be a the dependency
我提到的访问控制列表取决于它的版本
list for the access control list me
mention that it depends on a version of
这比Lists版本更远
this that's in the farther ahead than
the version of Lists the
死了，在那种情况下，警察可以通过一个问题来正确获取数据
begone and in that case cops GT would be
fetch the data alright with one question
与执行的威胁有关吗，是他们的因果关系
is it related to the threat of execution
yeah so it's true their causal
一致性不是真的与挂钟时间无关，所以它没有
consistency doesn't really it's not
about wall clock time so it has no
挂钟时间的概念只有唯一形式的命令
notion of wall clock time there's only
the only sort of forms of order that
服从甚至与步行时间有关，或者
it's obeying that are even a little bit
related to walk walk time or that if a
单线程做一件事，然后又做另一件事
single thread does one thing and then
another and another
那么因果一致性确实考虑了这三个操作
then causal consistency does consider
these three operations to be in that
顺序，但这是因为一个客户端线程执行了这些顺序的操作，而不是
order but it's because one client thread
did these sequence of things and not
因为存在实时关系，所以这里总结一下
because there was a real time
relationship so just a wrap up here to
某种程度地将其置于更大的范围内，因果一致性具有
sort of put this into a kind of larger
world context causal consistency has has
就像一个非常有前途的研究领域，已经有很长一段时间了
been an is like a very kind of promising
research area and has been for a long
时间，因为它似乎可以为您提供足够好的一致性
time because it does seem like it might
provide you with good enough consistency
而且还有更多的机会和线性化能力
but also opportunities more
opportunities and linearise ability to
获得高性能，但实际上并没有获得太大的吸引力
get high performance however it hasn't
actually gotten much traction in the
现实世界中的人们使用最终的一致性系统
real world
people use eventual consistency systems
他们使用高度一致的系统，但是很少看到部署
and they use strongly consistent systems
but it's very rare to see a deployed
系统和因果一致性，还有很多潜在的原因
system and as causal consistency and
there's a bunch of reasons potential
您知道的原因总是很难准确地说出人们为什么这样做或
reasons for that you know it's always
hard to tell exactly why people do or
不要在现实世界中使用某些技术，原因之一是
don't use some technology for real-world
systems one reason is that it can be
难以追踪用户和浏览器在现实世界中每个客户端的因果关系
awkward to track per client causality in
the real world a user and browser are
可能会在不同时间联系不同的Web服务器，这意味着
likely to contact different web servers
at different times and that means it's
单个Web服务器不足以保持用户上下文，我们需要某种方式
not enough for a single web server to
keep users context we need some way to
在单个用户访问不同的Web服务器时将其缝合在一起
stitch together context for a single
user as they visit different web servers
在同一个网站上，这很痛苦，我知道警察会遇到这个问题
at the same website so that's painful
I know there is this problem that cops
不不跟踪仅跟踪它知道的因果相关性
doesn't doesn't track only tracks causal
dependencies it knows about and that
意味着它没有铁定的解决方案或没有
means it doesn't doesn't have a sort of
ironclad solution or doesn't sort of
提供铁定的因果关系，并且仅提供某种因果关系
provide ironclad causality and only sort
of certain kinds of causality which is
很好的限制另一个吸引人的地方是您知道最终
well sort of limits how appealing it is
another is that the you know eventual
因果一致的系统只能提供最有限的概念
and causal consistent systems can
provide only the most limited notion of
我认为随着时间的流逝交易和人越来越多
transactions and people more and more I
think as time goes on are sort of
希望他们的存储系统有交易，我终于
wishing that their storage systems had
transactions I'm finally the amount of
推动轨道并存储所有依赖项所需的开销
overhead required to push around a track
and store all that dependency
信息可能非常重要，您知道我无法检测到
information can be quite significant and
you know I was unable to kind of detect
这在本文的性能部分中，但事实是很多
this in the performance section of the
paper but the fact is it's quite a lot
必须存储和推送的信息，您知道是否
of information that has to be stored and
pushed around and it you know if you
希望每秒可以进行数百万次操作
were hoping for the sort of millions of
operations per second level of
至少Facebook摆脱了内存缓存D的性能
performance that at least Facebook was
getting out of memcache D the kind of
使用因果一致性需要支付的开销可能是
overhead that you would have to pay to
use causal consistency might be
对于性能而言非常重要，所以这些就是为什么我
extremely significant for the
performance so those are reasons why I'm
因果一致性目前可能尚未流行，尽管也许
causal consistency maybe hasn't
currently caught on although maybe
总有一天我会说的没问题，实际上是从下一个开始
someday it will be okay that's all I
have to say and actually starting next
讲座中，我们将改变存储和顺序的齿轮
lecture we'll be switching gears away
from storage and sequence of three
涉及区块链的讲座，所以我星期四见
lectures that involve block chains so
I'll see you on Thursday
您
you